roberthalf.be 2016-12-15

# Privacy statement | Robert Half

This website ("Site") privacy statement ("Statement") describes how Robert Half BVBA/SPRL ("We", "we", or "RH") may use and disclose personally identifiable information that we may collect about you through the Site ("Personal Data").  
Robert Half BVBA/SPRL (Alfons Gossetlaan 28A, box 7; 1702 Groot-Bijgaarden) is responsible for the processing of your Personal Data, collected through this Site.  
By using this Site, you agree with the processing of your Personal Data in accordance with and as described in this Statement.

## Collections and Uses of Personal Data

When you use or register with the Site, we may ask for certain Personal Data. The categories of Personal Data we may request include your name and contact information (email, address and phone number). Depending on the nature of your inquiry or activities on the Site, we may also ask for your job search criteria and preferences, your employment experience, educational history, your skills, your salary, expectations, personality, references information, background information, other information contained in your resume, and any login ID and password created by you.  
Information about your health and/or court/criminal record is processed in accordance with the restrictions imposed by law and only if it is relevant to your application. If you provide Robert Half BVBA/SPRL with information about third parties, Robert Half BVBA/SPRL will assume that the third party in question has given you permission to do so and to Robert Half to collect, to process and to transfer their Personal Data to the same extent as yours.

The Site also utilizes cookies to track your online activities, including, but not limited to, registration, submissions, and information requests. A cookie is a small text file placed on your hard drive by our web page server. You can choose whether or not to use a cookie by altering the settings of your browser. A cookie will make the use of this Site faster and easier.  
You are giving Robert Half BVBA/SPRL permission to get in touch with the references you provided and to collect, process, transfer and use your Personal Data, including sensitive data, within the meaning described above, for such period as needed for achieving the purposes as set forth above

You declare that all information which you have provided or will provide to Robert Half BVBA/SPRL is true, correct and not misleading. Should any of this information change, you shall inform Robert Half BVBA/SPRL without any delay **.**

## Purposes of the processing of Personal Data

Robert Half BVBA/SPRL will process your Personal Data within the context of private employment mediation (temporary employment and/or recruitment), for the purpose of producing statistics and complying with regulations and to otherwise to provide you with requested information or services. Robert Half BVBA/SPRL may also use these Personal Data to inform you about its products and services unless you expressly state your opposition to this.

By accepting our Terms and Conditions you authorise Robert Half BVBA/SPRL to use your Personal Data for the purpose of sending you automated email messages or other electronic messages or marketing materials regarding our services, including employment information. You always have the opportunity to choose to no longer receive such messages or other direct marketing information by contacting Robert Half BVBA/SPRL via the following e-mail address: [reactions@rhi.net](mailto:reactions@rhi.net) or on the above mentioned postal address.

## Disclosures of Personal Data

RHI may disclose Personal Data to third parties including intra-group. The disclosure to third parties would occur in the following circumstances.  
We will disclose information to our clients where necessary and appropriate in connection with the provision of staffing services.  
We may disclose information to companies and individuals we employ to perform business functions and services on our behalf. Such functions may include, for example, hosting our Web servers, analyzing data, providing legal, accounting and marketing services.

We may disclose information to the extent necessary or appropriate to government agencies, advisors, and other third parties in order to comply with applicable laws, the service of legal process, or if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary to (a) comply with the law requiring such disclosure; (b) protect the rights or property of RHI or its affiliated companies; (c) prevent a crime or protect national security or (d) protect the personal safety of the users or the public.

## Transfer of Personal Data outside the European Economic Area ("EEA")

Robert Half BVBA/SPRL is part of an international group of companies operating globally; Robert Half BVBA/SPRL may also communicate your Personal Data to third parties and other group companies of Robert Half, including its parent company Robert Half International Inc. in the United States, who may use or process your Personal Data for the same purpose as described above.

You are giving Robert Half BVBA/SPRL permission to transfer your collected and held Personal Data to any country, including countries outside the EEA, which may not have an adequate level of data protection, for any of the purposes as described in this Statement.

## Right of access to and correction of Personal Data

If you wish to make use of your right to consult and correct your Personal Data, to object against the use of your Personal Data for direct marketing purposes or if you have any other questions in connection with their being processed, please get in touch with Robert Half BVBA/SPRL; Alfons Gossetlaan 28A, box 7; 1702 Groot-Bijgaarden.

## Revisions to the Statement

If we change this privacy statement we will post any updates here for your review. If we change material terms in this Statement, we will provide notice of the revised statement for 30 days on the home page at www.roberthalf.be with a link back to this page.
